<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/agb_textView"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="500dp"
        android:layout_margin="16dp"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        android:text="Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. Scrollable TextView in android application, how to make android textview scroollable without using scrollview. gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggg" />

    <CheckBox
        android:id="@+id/agb_checkbox"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="CheckBox" />

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/porceed"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Button" />

</LinearLayout>